片名：最终幻想之灵魂深处
梦已记录  2065年12月13日
每天晚上同样的梦  同样的怪异星球
Every night, the same dream. The same strange planet.
但是为什么
But why?
他们想告诉我什么
What are they trying to tell me?
他们到这个星球已有34年
It has been 34 years since they arrived in this planet.
被迫移居到堡垒城市的幸存者  没有一天不是在恐惧中度过
And now the days passes, the survivors forced to live in a barrier cities.
我发誓要结束这种恐惧
Do not live in fear. I have vowed to the end that fear.
我的梦就是解决一切的钥匙
I believe my dreams hold the key.
问题是我还来得及拯救地球吗
The question is, Will I be in time to save the Earth?
旧纽约城
你在哪?
Where are you?
这是限制区域
This is a restricted area.
别动
Do not move!
-她在这做什么  上尉?-我不知道。我们在带她出去。
-What is she doing here, captain? -I don't know, but we are getting her out.
-你跟我们一起走 -在你后面
-You're coming with us. -Behind you!
抓住它
Hold it right there!
该死的  行动吧
Damn it! Let's move, people.
有两个从墙穿过来
Two, coming through the wall.
别开枪  那些桶容易起火
Alright, hold your fire.
莱恩  尼尔  我们走吧
Ryan, Neil, let's go.
-你究竟在做什么 -这有一种生命形式
-What the hell do you think you are doing? -There is a life form in here.
-这里已经多年没有生命体了 -但是现在有
-There hasn't been life here in years. -There is now.
是不是生命形式  我要带你回去
Life form or not, I'm not leaving without that life form.
逮捕我  但不带上它我是不会走的
Gonna be one of those days.
没办法  算了吧
上尉  交通舰不会等我们那么长时间的
Captain, principal is not going to wait any much longer.
我明白
I understand that.
很不好
It's in bad shape.
告诉我我们不是为了这株植物玩命的
Please. Tell me when I am risking for this plant.
我都不会把它叫做植物  一棵野草而已
I won't even call it a plant. It's wheat.
我都不会把它叫做野草
I won't even call it a wheat.
我需要一分钟把它取出来
I need a minute to extract it.
小姐  我们恰好没有这一分钟了
Miss, that's the minute we do not have.
恐怕他是对的
I'm afraid his right about that, ma'am.
幽灵  我们有敌人了
Captain, we have incomings.
-上尉  我们要行动了 -明白  中士
-Captain, we need to get out from here. -Understood, sergeant.
-能不能快点  小姐 -完成
-Could you hurry please, miss? -Done
-上尉 -怎么  尼尔
-Captain. -Yes, Neil.
我同意  我们快离开这里
Just all you know, I agree with. Let's get out from here.
非常同意
能给我这个吗?谢谢
Can I have this please? Thank you.
-我们被包围了 -噢  混蛋
-We're surrounded. -No! Shit!
-大家别紧张 -上尉  我们得到高处去
-Alright, everybody. Just relax. -Captain, we got to get to higher ground.
每个人  到上面去
Everyone, up to top.
快  快  快！
Go! Go! Go!
-交通舰  要求立即撤退 -收到
-Transport requesting immediately event. -Confirm.
上这里来
Up here!
-上尉…上尉  快点… -我们就在你后面
-Captain! -We are right behind you.
我抓住你了
I got you.
-你没事吧 -还好
- Are you okay? - Yeah.
大家注意  他们来了
Alright, everybody. Here they come.
你没事吗
Are you okay?
你会没事的
为什么我不能把你抓起来呢
Can you give me one good reason why I shouldn't arrest you?
我是阿琪・罗斯博士  我有到这里来的许可
I am Dr. Aki Ross. I have clearance to be here.
不是无限的许可  没有授权…
Not unlimited clearance. And not without authorization.
我没时间说这些
Captain, I don't have time for this.
你知道吗?你在拿我这班战士的命冒险
Do you realize you have just risk the lives at my squad and me?
听着  我不想说  但事实是
Look. I don't want to talk about it. The fact of the matter is,
牺牲你和你手下这些男人的生命也值得
it was worth the lives of you and your men.
“你和你手下这些男人”?
You and your men?
-她认为你是男人 -我认为她是白痴
-She thinks you are a man. -I think she's an idiot.
-我知道你不是男人 -我认为你也是白痴
-I know you are not a man. -I think you're an idiot too.
有趣
Very funny.
我正想谈谈
But I do want to talk about it.
你就没想过  给我们选择机会  我们会自愿的
Did it occur to you that maybe we are not volunteer to risk our lives?
没人让你救我
Nobody asked you to save me.
我真不敢相信  你一点也没变
I can't believe this. You have not changed a bit.
格雷
Gray?
见到你很高兴
Yeah, nice to see you too.
第42号堡垒城市：纽约市
-欢迎回来  上尉 -我们很干净
-Welcome back, captain. -We're cleaned.
-我们要确定一下 -我讨厌接受扫描
-Let's make sure of this, shall we? -I hate getting scanned.
对我们来说  这也许比幽灵还要糟
Sir, the scan probably worth to us than the phantoms..
有人怀疑这些机器可能会引起不育症
This machine are suspected to causing sterility.
我可还想有朝一日有个小尼尔叫我爸爸
And I want to have a little new junior to call me daddy someday.
-是个大胆的想法 -你为什么总是挖苦我?
-That's a spooky thought. -Why are you always busting my chop?
让我们都来扫描  好吗
People, let's just do this thing. Alright.
-是  长官 -是  长官
- Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
好  下一位
Okay, next.
你胖了
Looks like you gain some weight.
这叫上身的力量  尼尔  找个女朋友吧
It's called body strength, Neil. Get a girlfriend.
我在努力
I'm working on it.
你知道我的安全级别允许我不用扫描
You know my security rating allows me to bypass this.
今天不行
Not today, it doesn't.
有些不对劲
Something's not right.
-关于这次任务还是那个女人 -都有
-About this mission or that woman? - Both.
下一位
Next.
听着  上尉  我想…
Listen, captain. I think...
我不管你想什么  博士
I don't care what you think, doctor.
你也要接受检查  就像其他人一样
You're getting scanned just like everybody else.
混蛋
Oh shit!
-上尉 -他感染了幽灵
-Captain! -They got him.
一定出错了
There must be a mistake.
你曾经与幽灵接触过  长官
You came in contact with the phantom, sir.
请保持镇静
Please remain calm.
启用防护盾
Administering treatment shield.
-他在什么水平 -蓝色  3分半钟后会变到红色
-What level is he? -Blue. He will be coded at 3 1/2 minutes.
我们必须现在给他治疗
We have to treat him now.
抱歉  但是不行  我们要把他转到治疗中心
I'm sorry. That's impossible. We'll transfer him to the treatment center.
没时间了
There's no time for that.
把他扶到桌子上
Take him to the table.
坚持住  上尉
Hang on, captain.
确定病原体位置
Locating particles.
天哪  看
Jesus! Look at that thing.
还有多少时间
How much more time?
不够了  他到达红色区时  防护盾也不能封锁病原体了
Not enough. When he reaches code red, the treatment shield won't be able to hold the aliens particles
使用生物激光
Engaging bio-ethereal laser.
-出什么事了? -它跑哪去了?
- What's going on? - Where does it go?
究竟出什么事了
What the hell is going on?
失去跟踪了  感染正向深处发展了
We lost contact. Infer station is moving deeper.
-追踪 -没时间了
- Dragging. - There is no time.
- Dragging. - There is no time!
你救不活他的
You're gonna lose him.
他的防护盾正在减弱
发现了
Founded.
快点
没事了
It's alright.
不用担心  你很快就会恢复的
Don't worry. You'll be back to normal in no time.
博士我们要检查你是否被感染
Doctor, we need to scan you for in infer station.
那就不必了  我会负责的
That won't be necessary. I'll take responsibility.
博士
Hey, Doc.
谢谢你救了他
Thanks for saving him.
-你没事吧 -嗯  但军方没收了我的宇航船
-Are you alright? -Yeah, but the military has impounded my ship
她有什么秘密
What's with her?
她和上尉之间有什么秘密
And what's with her with the captain?
她和那傻植物之间有什么秘密
What's with her and the stupid plan?
什么
What?
给我幽灵数据  以及关于五个灵魂  我们到现在为止收集到的一切资料
Forward me the phantom data and everything we got in the file spirits collected so far.
是  博士
Yes, Doctor.
我想我们不应该用复数词
Spirits? I thought we are not suppose to use the S word.
别跟我较真
Don't get smart with me.
现在看看这株植物能为我们做什么
Let's see if the plant does the trick.
提取植物波形
匹配可能的波形
匹配
是匹配的  我们找到了
It's a match. We've found it.
是的  第六个灵魂
Yes, the 6th spirit.
你几乎违反了每个协议
A little scene today brought me every protocol
你认为在堡垒城外它能存活多久
How long do you think this would have survive outside the barrier?
有人正等着把我们排斥在外
Aki, you know there are elements in the Council military just waiting for an excuse to shut us down.
10年前谁在幽灵身上发现了这种能量?是你
Look. 1 0 years ago, who discovered the energy and the phantoms? You.
谁证明这种能量存在人类和一切生命形式中
And who proved the same energy source existed in humans and every life form?
还是你  你也使控制这种能量成为可能
You.  You made the possible to harness that energy
并且用于“卵包”、扫描器甚至堡垒城
for overpacks, scanners, even the barrier.
委员会知道  他们信任你  我们就要证实…
The Council knows that. They trust you, Doctor. We are so close to proving...
我们还需要这些
We still need this part and this one here.
对  再有两块就揭开谜底了
Exactly. Two more pieces and we solve the puzzle.
我们要解决思想才能找到
We need to be free to find these pieces.
我给你看样东西  阿琪
I want to show you something, Aki.
-这是什么 -念
- What is this? - Read.
所有生命都源于盖亚  每个生命有一个灵魂
All life is born of Gaya and each life has a spirit.
每种灵魂都有寄存于一个物质的身体… 博士
Each new spirit is housed in physical body. Doctor...
继续
Go on.
通过他们在地球的经历  每个灵魂会成熟长大
Through their experiences on Earth, the spirits mature and grows.
当肉体死亡
When the physical body dies,
充实了地球上的经历  成熟的灵魂返回盖亚
the mature spirit enrich by it's life on Earth returns to Gaya.
把经验也随之带走  让盖亚能够存活成长
Bring in with it the experiences, enabling Gaya to live and grow.
这是我的日记
To my old diary.
我43年写的  那里我像你现在一样大
I wrote that 43 years ago when I was the age you are now.
希德博士
Dr. Sid!
还记的伽里略吗  被关进监狱
I don't know what happen to Gary Will. They threw him into jail
只是因为他说地球不是宇宙的中心
because he said that Earth was not descendant of the universe.
我们也会有同样的遭遇
That could happen to us.
我们的观点并不普及  阿琪
Our ideas are unpopular, Aki.
如果你有不利于你的记录
If you have any notes or records, it could be used against you.
销毁掉
Destroy them.
-保存在这里 -好的
-Keep them up here. -Right.
离你那上尉朋友远点
And stay away from your friend, that captain.
他救了你的命  你救了他的  一来二去
He saves your life, you save his life. That's least to that.
我也曾年轻过
I was once young too, you know.
博士  战争正在进行
Doctor, there is a war going on.
没有人会再年轻了
No one is young anymore.
委员会的女士们、先生们
Could you please explain why Zeus cannon was completed a month ago.
请你们解释一下
宙斯炮一个月前就完成了
如果我们攻击陨星  我们会从根本上消灭幽灵
If we attack their media with this, we will eliminate the phantoms at their source.
海因将军  冷静
General Hein, calm down.
上次会议我们表决6对2
At our last meeting, we voted 6 to 2 to postpone using the Zeus cannon.
延迟使用宙斯炮攻击狮子座陨星
To attack alienated media.
我们开会就是要再次就此事表决
We have reconvince today to vote on that very issue again.
我要让生物中心的指挥讲一讲
Now I would like to ask the director of the bio-ethereal center to speak.
希德博士  请
Dr Sid, please.
谢谢
正如你们所知  幽灵的巢在…
As you all know, the phantom nested
34年前到这里的狮子座陨星
the alienated media that landed here 34 years ago.
你们现在看到的是对陨星的每次攻击记录
What you see now, are the records of assault on the media to date.
物理攻击毫无效果
Physical attacks here had no affect.
这是三月前的一次全面轰炸
This seems to place 3 months ago joining a full scale of art.
请注意陨星以外的幽灵确实被消灭了
Please note that the phantom outside the media are indeed destroyed.
然而许多原来在陨星内部休眠的却被激活了生命
However inside, many that come to live.
如你们看到的  总体上幽灵密度也没有改变
And as you see over all phantom density remains the same.
异星生物应对这种攻击的方法是
The newly recent aliens response to the attack.
潜入地球更深处
By burly, even deeper into the Earth.
我对此很有兴趣  希德博士
Now this is very interesting to me, Dr. Sid.
因为我们看到了在手术中看到同样的事
Because we see the same thing during surgery.
当我们对幽灵分子使用生物激光束不也遇到类似的情况吗?
When using bio-ethereal laser on phantom particles. Do we not?
是的  确实如此
Yes, indeed we do.
受伤的分子逃跑了
You see the injured escape,
逃向病人身体深处
burying or digging themselves deeper into the patient body.
我们增加激光能量破坏这些深入的分子时
When we increase the laser power to destroy these deep particles.
会导致病人更大的伤害
We have had incidents resulting and further injury to a patient.
有时候  甚至是死亡
And in some cases, death.
这到底意味着什么  博士
And what exactly does that mean, Doctor?
这意味着很有可能
It means there is a very good chance to
宙斯炮的光束会烧掉陨星上的幽灵
being from the Zeus cannon built in the phantoms in a media.
正是这样  谢谢
Exactly. Thank you.
光束能量也许太强  会破坏地球
However, it also means that the being energy maybe too strong injuring the Earth.
破坏地球?
Injure the Earth?
你是说盖亚
You mean the spirit of the Earth?
-我是说… -你是说地球的灵魂?
Yes. The spirit of the Earth.
是的
地球的灵魂
他说什么?
你在做什么
我知道我在做什么  闭嘴
I know what I'm doing. And whatever you do, keep you mouth shut.
这太荒谬了
This is ridiculous.
博士  以您所有的威望
Doctor, with all the respect.
你是来谈盖亚理论的吗
You come here just to talk about some Gaya theory?
告诉我们这个星球是活的
Tell us the planet is alive?
有一个灵魂
Has a spirit?
那是童话  很遗憾我们没有时间
That's a fairy tale, Doctor. Sorry, but we don't have time for that.
那不是童话  是真的
It's not a fairy tale, it's true.
如果我对地球开一枪
So if I point a gun to the Earth and fire,
我不只打出个洞  而是在杀害地球
I'm not just making a hole on the ground, I am killing the planet.
希德博士  盖亚理论还没证明
Dr. Sid, the Gaya theory has not been proven.
即使盖亚存在  我们不是还要把幽灵移走吗
Even the Gaya does exist. We still have to remove the phantoms.
有成功的机会我们就要抓住
I think if there is any chance of success. We should take it.
-你同意吗? -当然
- Don't you agree? - Of course I do.
但是除了太空大炮外  还有种选择
But there is an alternative to this space cannon
另一种
Another method?
-使幽灵失去能力的一种方法  -请说
-Yes, I mean of disabling the phantoms. -Please.
众所周知外星人表现出一种独特的能量形式
we know that the aliens display distinct energy pattern
两个相对的生物被  互相叠加  彼此削弱
Now it is a fact that two bio-ethereal waves places one over the other will cancel each other out.
理论上可以合成一种  与幽灵能量正好相反的波形
It's the erectile possible to construct the wave pattern direct opposition to the phantom energy.
我们正合成这种被并且即将完成
We are currently assembling...
诸位委员会成员  从全世界收集植物和动物
Members of the Council, gathering plants and animals
来对抗幽灵实在是一派胡言
from around the world to fight the phantoms is other nonsense.
加农炮是一种已经证实有效的武器
The Zeus cannon is a proven effective weapon.
会杀死幽灵
It will kill phantoms.
我们还能等什么疯狂的发明吗
Can we afford to wait for some crazy inventions
敏感的植物和动物的大军
Some army of touchy feeling plants and animals
而对消灭异星生物根本起不到什么作用
An invention with no solid evidence that will destroy the aliens.
有证据
There is evidence.
我们部分完成的能量波已经
Our partially completed energy wave has
成功阻止了一位持久性感染的病人体内幽灵的扩散
a terminally successfully stopped phantom particles from spreading through a terminally infected patient.
博士  你能证据表明这位病人已经治愈吗
Doctor, do you claim to have evidence that terminally patient has been cured.
没有治愈  波还没完成
Not cured. The wave is not completed.
但我们已经成功将分子控制在病人体内
But we have succeeded in containing the particles safely inside the patient.
证据在哪里呢
Where is the proof?
这里
Here.
阿琪  也许你为我们争取到一些时间  但是以什么代价呢
You may have bothered sometime, Aki. But I wonder what caused?
博士  你保护我时我也不能总躲在后面
Doctor, I can't keep hiding in the background while you protect me.
我也要让我所剩下的生命有意义
I want what life I have left to mean something.
听着  当我们发现第七第八灵魂
You listen to me. When we find the 7th and 8th spirits...
如果能发现  我们现在需要的是运气
If we find them, what we need now is some luck.
运气一点也没有用
Luck has nothing to do with it.
信念与勤奋  姑娘
Fate and hard work, girl.
因为你要在我之前死去  我会受诅咒的
Cause I'll be damn if you die before me.
委员会决定推迟使用宙斯炮
The Council decided to postpone firing the Zeus cannon.
我猜因我演了场好戏
I guess I put on a good show.
如果我也跟着不介意吧
Mind if I take a look?
你会觉得无聊的
You'll probably get bored.
那么  那你在做什么
So what are you doing?
我明白了  你是无声的抗议
Oh, I see. Giving me the silent treatment.
我在扫描这城市  以寻找第七灵魂
I am scanning the city for the 7th spirit.
快点  尼尔
Hurry up, Neil.
-差不多了 -你在做什么
-I almost got it. -What do you think you are doing?
我们想让他们一起呆一会
We just gonna strengthen them for a while.
别看我  这是他的主意
Hey, don't look at me. It was his idea.
是你的主意
It's your idea?
我们正在帮助上尉
We just help the captain up a little.
简  你的浪漫细胞呢
Come on, Jane. Where's your sense of romance?
你看到了上尉看她的样子
You see how the captain looks at her.
懂吗  孩子
It's a more, baby.
发生什么了
What's going on?
也许哪出了点小毛病
Probably just a glint.
-我说  阿琪… -我对你仍然很生气
- Listen, Aki... - I'm still mad at you.
-你疯了? -你不摘下头盔  也不告诉我你是谁
-You are mad at me? -Leaving your helmet on and not telling me who you were?
那太孩子气了吧
That doesn't seem a little childish.
你去宙斯站时一句话也没说  我很伤心
I was just a little upset when you dispatched and leave the Zeus station without saying a word.
-现在你知道发生什么了 -是的
-Now you know what's going on, alright? -Now I know.
我的工作必须在零重力下进行
My operation had to be done in zero graph, okay?
好
Fine!
我到那去办事时你甚至不来看我
How about the fact that I was sent there on the job and you won't even see me?
我也许正在帮助希德博士收集灵魂波
I was probably helping Dr. Sid collected the spirit wave.
-现在我知道了 -对不起
-Now I know. -So I'm sorry.
我也是  我俩一样
Well, me too. So we are both sorry.
你能讲讲他们吗
So would you tell me about them?
关于什么
About what?
你收集的灵魂啊
About the spirits you collected.
在一次实验中我被幽灵感染了
I was infected by the phantom during an experiment.
-一般无人会活下来 -你怎么做到的呢
-Normally no one could had survived. -How could you?
西德博士在感染区制造了保护膜  我才活了下来
Dr. Sid created a memory around the infection keeping me alive.
因此第一个灵魂波是我
So the first spirit wave was me.
第二个是条鱼
The second was a fish.
鱼
A fish?
第三个是头鹿  我在莫斯科郊外的野生动物保护区发现的
The third was a deer I found in a wildlife-preserved outside Moscow.
第四个是只鸟
The fourth was a bird.
你试过在外太空追踪一只麻雀吗  一点也不好玩
Ever try to track a sparrow out of space? It's no fun.
-不管我怎么说  你也许会喜欢上的 -是  我也许会的
-What am I saying? You probably would love that. -You are right. I probably would.
然后就是我从时代广场收集的那植物
And then there was that plant I collected from Time Square.
-我想那是第六个了 -什么
-I thought that was number 6. -What?
你漏了一个
You skipped one.
第五是医院急救室里垂危的一个小女孩
The fifth was a little girl dying in a hospital emergency room.
我及时抽取了标本  但她…
I retrieved the disabling time, but she...
我告诉她一切都有灵魂  狗、猫、树、小女孩
I told her everything has a spirit. Dogs, cats, trees, little girls,
甚至是地球
even the earth.
我说她不会死  只是回到地球的灵魂――盖亚
I told her that she wasn't dying, just returning to the Earth spirit. The Gaya.
她跟我说她准备死
She... told me that she was ready to die.
她说我不必编故事哄她开心
She said I didn't have to make up stories to make her feel better.
只有7岁就要死了
Only 7 years old and ready to die.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我有事要做  我一定要找到第七第八灵魂
I have work to do. I have to find the 7th and the 8th spirits.
请不要
Don't... please....
你一点也不相信这些  是吗
You don't believe any of this, do you?
我只是不知道  阿琪
I just... don't know, Aki.
这就是为什么你拒绝我
Is this why you shut me out?
你该告诉我
You should have told me.
我不知我还有多少时间
I don't know how much time I left.
谁知道
Who does?
我最好回来继续扫描的工作
I better get back to scanning.
爱德华上尉
Captain Edwards,
你几天前从旧纽约救了一个罗丝博士  对吗
you extracted a Dr. Ross from old New York several days ago. Did you not?
-是的  长官 -你对罗丝博士印象如何
What were you impressions of Dr Ross?
她显得非常干练坚毅
She seems very capable and determines.
现在给你和深邃眼睛小队暂时分配一个任务
You and the Deep Eyes are being temporary reassigned.
罗丝博士再去荒原时  你保护她
You will guard Dr. Ross when she re-enters the waste land.
明白  长官
Understood, sir.
你还不明白  上尉
You don't understand yet, Captain.
罗丝博士有任何异常举动  立即报告少校
Report any ebullient behavior in Dr Ross to the Major immediately.
异常行为  长官?
Ebullient behavior, sir?
她被这异星生物感染  我们不知这对她有何影响
The woman carries an alien infer station, captain. We don't know what it maybe doing to her.
异星生物的存在也许影响她的判断
The aliens presence could be effecting her judgement.
也许会控制她以实现它们的目的
And maybe manipulate the Doctor for their very own purposes
将军怀疑罗丝博士是间谍?
Is the General suggesting that Dr Ross is a spy?
将军在奇怪他为什么要亲自向一名上尉解释
The General is wondering why he explains himself to a captain.
她长时间的暴露在幽灵组织下
She separated long exposure to phantom tissue
如果这开始显露
If this begins to manifest itself in anyway,
罗丝博士将会被逮捕并送到这里来观察
Dr Ross is to be placed under arrest. And transport here for observation.
事实上这是为了她好  上尉
It is in fact for her own good, captain.
当然  长官
Of course, sir.
少校  安排一些我们的人看着上尉
Major, send some of our man to keep an eye on our good captain.
我认为这些梦是信息传达的一种方式
I'm convinced these dreams are some form of communication.
只是我还在困惑它们表达什么
The message still elude to me.
但它们来得更快了  这只能意味着一件事
But they are coming faster now. And that can only mean one thing.
我体内的幽灵开始占上风
The phantoms inside me are beginning to win
-我们的目标是图森以西50米 -收到
-Our target is to discrete at two sign. -Roger.
-幽灵密度? -不好  到处都是巨型的
-Phantom concentration. Not good. -We got big minutes everywhere.
将会是场硬仗
So it's gonna be a real picnic.
跟紧我  不要逞英雄  一切按书本
Stick close to me. No heroin today, okay? Everything by the book.
按照书本  是的
By the book, alright.
图森荒原
如果我们丢下能量标在这里  这里  和这里
If we drop energy here, here and here.
我们就能获得目标并在他们发现我们以前离开
We should be able quiet at the target and get out even before the phantoms know we were there.
能量标会吸引幽灵?
And that would attract the phantoms.
-是的 -只是一会
For a while.
你是从第307号来的  海因将军的部下
So you are from the 307s, right? Under General Hein?
以前做过荒原侦察吗?可能很难看的
Have you done any wasteland recon before? And get pretty ugly.
长官  撤退的集合点在航线6、坐标279
Captain, rendezvous at sector 6 coded 279.
收到  注意警惕敌人
Roger that. Stellar for hard files.
看来他们中了陷阱
Looks like they are taking a bath.
第七幽灵应该在失事地点附近
The 7th spirit should be just beyond the line.
生物如何在这里生存?
I don't see how any living thing could survive out here.
很快我们就会知道
You'll find out soon enough.
这里曾是清除幽灵战役
This was the phantom cleansing mission.
本来是用来结束战争的
It was supposed the end of war.
我的父亲就在这里的某个地方
My father is in here somewhere.
好了
Alright.
我们过去吧  各位
Let's move out, people.
我完了
I'll be damn.
一个生存者
A survivor.
它在这里干什么?
What is it doing out here?
希望生命能回来
Hoping for life to return.
那是我们的灵魂吗  博士? -不
-Is that our spirit, Doc? - No.
我们正在接近那生命形态
We've closing in on a life form.
-距离? -很难说  我们很近了
Distance?Hard to say.We are very close.
我看不到任何东西
I don't see anything.
-你不会告诉我是他吧?-那是不可能的
-You're not gonna tell me it's him. -That's impossible
不是这个士兵  是他的“卵包”
It's not the soldier. It's his overpack.
怎么会?“卵包”给我们的武器和堡垒城市等提供能源
How do you explain that? Packs? Power or weapon? The barrier cities?
这只是生化能源
I mean it's just by with theory energy.
我们是用生物组织来制造能源的  单细胞的生物
And to create that energy, we use living tissue. Single cell organism.
-他的背包就是第七幽灵? -是的
-You're telling me his backpack is the 7th spirit. -Yes.
有情况  上尉  你听到我吗?
Captain, do you read me?
再说一次?
Once again.
有敌人来了
Captain, we have incoming.
莱恩  去拿士兵的卵包
Ryan, get the soldier's pack.
我需要帮手  中士
I need a hand, sergeant.
-那些能量标?他们没用了 -是的  谢谢
- Those boys. -Yeah. Thank you.
-你没事吧? -当然
Are you alright? -Of course I am.
我们离开这里吧
Let's get the hell out of here.
有些不对劲  这不应该发生
Something is not right. It should be happening.
有东西在吸引他们
Something are tracking them.
阿琪！
Aki...
-它们正在追我们  靠近得很快 -简  你领路
-There are right on us, sir. -Closing fast.Jane, take the lead.
我要发射啦！
Fire the hole!
带我们离开这里  尼尔
Get us out of here, Neil.
-长官  我很想  可是… -快点
Sir, I would love to. But... - Just do it!
好了  原来是这样
- Sir? - Locate that seat.
看上去不好  上尉
That doesn't look good, captain.
我们得把她带去医院
We have to get her to a hospital.
-你必须遵守命令  长官 -到底这么回事?
-You have your order, sir. -What the hell is happening here?
罗斯博士现在被收留了
Dr Ross is to be taken into the custody now.
放下你的武器  这是命令！
Lower your weapon. That's an order.
长官  我们别无选择  只能撤销你的指挥权
We have no choice but to relief you and your command.
我不会让你这么做的  除非你射击我
I won't let you do this, soldier. You'll gonna have to shoot me.
退后  上尉！
Bend down, captain!
阿琪！
Aki!
大家坚持住！
Hang on, everyone!
够了  所有人  把手举到我看得见的地方  现在！
That's enough! Everyone down.
深遂眼睛  右满舵！
尼尔  尽快把我们送回纽约！
Neil, get us back to New York. Fast.
深遂眼睛小队从荒原回来了  长官
The device are returned from the wasteland, sir.
显然发生了一件事
Apparently there was an incident.
幽灵都被罗斯博士吸引了
It would seem the phantoms were attracted to Dr Ross.
小队人员险些没能逃出
The crew barely escaped with their lives.
而且  长官  爱德华上尉仍然是指挥者
And sir... Captain Edward is still in command.
发布一个命令
Issue an order.
我要逮捕爱德华和罗斯博士
I want Edward and Dr Ross to be place under arrest.
与希德博士的波理论有关的所有研究资料立即全部没收
All research materials pretending to Dr Sid wave theoryare to be confiscated immediately.
这可能和委员会有冲突
That might not go over too well with the Council, sir.
真是个悲剧啊
What a tragedy that would be.
这真完美  少校  这位好上尉为我们提供了机会
This is perfect, Major. It's too good the captain has opened the door for us.
到明天早上  委员会会服从我们
By tomorrow morning, the Council would bear our feet.
感谢我们揭示出背叛者
Thanking us for exposing the traitors and imploring us.
并恳求我们从幽灵手中救他们出来
To save them from the phantoms.
她怎么样了  博士?
How is she, Doctor?
-她快死了 -你一定要救她
-She is dying. -There must be something you can do.
阿琪在和6个幽灵作战
Aki is fighting with only the 6th and 8th spirits.
我们得将第七个装置在她的胸板
We have to implant the 7th directly into her chest plate.
那里中了一枪  它可能坏了
It took a bullet. I think it might be damage.
我们得尽快修理这个胸板
We have to appear this panel quickly.
她的生命迹象正在减弱  阿琪快离开我们了
Her vital signs are dropping. Aki is slipping away from us.
她需要一个有同情心的灵魂把她留在这个世界
She needs a sympathetic spirit to help her held hold in this world.
我想没有谁比你更合适这任务了  上尉
And I can think of no spirit but to suit for that task but yours, captain.
-我不明白 -你不需要明白
-I don't understand. -You don't have to understand.
现在你只要和她在一起
You just be with her now.
你将她留下来
You'll keep her here with us.
阿琪?我们在哪?
Aki, where are we?
在一个外星球
On an alien planet.
这怎么可能?
How is that possible?
我也不确定
I'm not entirely sure.
你看来很平静
You seem pretty calm.
几个月来我每天做这个梦
I have been having this dream every night for months.
做梦?
Dream?
不管它是什么
Well, whatever it is.
你真的在这里  是吗?
You're really here, aren't you?
我到底发生了什么事?
What's happening to me?
希德在你身上装入第七个幽灵
Dr Sid is implanting the 7th spirit directly into your body.
那你就是我的心灵助手
Then you are my spiritual support.
格雷  你真好
Gray, how sweet of you.
我想你不明白事情有多严重
I don't think you realize how serious this situation is.
你应该看这里的东西  长官
Something you should see here, sir.
我看的是什么  少校?
And I am watching... what, major?
罗斯博士好象记录了她的梦
It seems Dr Ross has been recording her dreams.
我为什么要对她的梦感兴趣?
And why would I be interested in it... her dreams?
这就是我们的证据
This is it. This is our evidence.
她在幽灵的控制下
She's under influence of the phantoms.
罗斯博士  这些梦可以让委员会批准宙斯大炮
Dr Ross's dreams should be all the Council needs authorize the firing of the Zeus cannon.
委员会宁愿躲在堡垒里面
The Council is contempt to hide powering inside this barrier
坐视世界一天一天的死亡
while the world dies a little more everyday.
我认为需要在正确的方向上推动他们一下
I believe they need a push in the right direction, major.
请你组织一群最可靠的人
Get another a group of your most trusted men.
他们在干什么?他们为什么看着我们?
What are they doing? Why are they staring at us?
不是看我们
Not at us.
欢迎回来  上尉
Welcome back, captain.
结束了吗?
Is it over?
她怎么样  博士?
How is she, Doctor?
她没事  可是这是短期的
She is going to be fine. But this is only temporary.
我们需要找到第八个和最终的灵魂才能救她
We need to find the 8th and final spirit to cure her.
阿琪  听得到我吗?
Aki, can you hear me?
我完成了
I'd finished it.
我知道它的意思
我知道幽灵是什么了
I know what the phantoms really are.
不许动！你们都被逮捕了！
Nobody move! You are all under arrest!
我们已经逮捕他们了  长官
We have them, sir.
长官?
Sir?
我的妻子和女儿…
My wife and daughter.
在旧金山堡垒城被幽灵杀了
Were killed by phantoms in San Francisco when the city was attacked.
我告诉过你吗?
Did I ever tell you that?
我试着去想象
I try to imagine what...
你周围的人没理由的死去
How is that like seeing everyone around you, fall over dead with no apparent reason.
最后  你感到有东西在旁边
And then at the end, you're feeling something next to you.
看不见  触动你
Invisible... touching you.
进到你的身体
Reaching inside your body.
你也曾失去了家人  是吗?
You've lost family, haven't you?
是的  先生
Yes, sir.
所以我信任你
That's why I trust you.
你们全部
All for you.
你们知道应该做的事
You know what must be done.
堡垒控制中心
覆盖安全限制
侵入周边
出什么事了?
少校  逮捕这些人
Major, arrest these man.
放松点站起来．去
你可以休息了  别问问题
降低到第31区的能源
Reduce power to sector 31.
长官  你应该知道幽灵…
Sir, you do realize that the phantoms...
我知道的是  少校…我们得强迫委员会去行动
What I realize, major is that we must force the Council to take action against the enemy.
阿尔法能源通道的25%已转移
25% % of energy redirect.
降低到第31区的能源
Over ring power put to sector 31.
第31区的屏障被破坏  将军  他们过来了
Bury the bridge in sector 31, General. They're coming through now.
我们能应付几个在封闭空间里的幽灵
I think we can easily handle a few phantoms in a contain space.
放松  少校  今晚结束后  你就会成为一个英雄
Relax, major. When this night is over, you are going to be a hero.
-阿琪  我不认为… -你在我的梦里  格雷  你看到了
-Aki, I don't think... -You were in my dream, Gray. You saw it. That's just it.
我不确定我看到的是什么  你如何确定?
I'm not sure what I saw. How can you be?
上尉  请让她继续
Captain, please. Let her continue.
你想我们为何不能知道
Why do you think, we've never been able to determine
像人一样大的幽灵和在荒原上活动的大幽灵之间的关系?
a relationship between the human size phantoms. And the giant one's roaming away slants.
对不起  博士  究竟是什么关系?
Excuse me, Doc. But frequent relationship.
你有像人一样大的幽灵  毛虫一样爬的幽灵
I mean you got your human size phantoms and your creepy caterpillary phantoms.
会飞的幽灵  别忘了还有我喜欢的
And your flying phantoms. And let's not forget my personal favorite.
肥大幽灵
The big fat giant phantoms...
-坐下  小子 -他说得对
-Down, boy. - He's right.
如果你像我们在战场时间久了
If you spend as much time in this field as we have.
你就知道没什么关系  那里好象一个动物园
You know there is no relationship. Is like a zoo out there.
正是如此  我想巨型幽灵象我们的鲸鱼或大象
Precisely, I think the giant ones are like our whales along for the ride?
那为什么一个军队会带些鲸鱼和大象来入侵?
除非他们的船象疯狂的挪亚方舟?
It must be the ship of some kind crazy known as ark.
我们一直以为陨星是用作交通工具的
We always assume that the media was intended as a form of transportation.
但不是
Perhaps it wasn't.
陨星是它们星球的一部分  当他们毁灭了它们的世界时被抛进了宇宙里
The media is a chunk of their planet. They got thrown into space when they destroyed their world.
可是在外太空旅行时它们如何在一大块石头上生存?
But how could they survive the trip across outer space on a hunk of rock?
它们没有生存下来
They didn't.
噢  听上去有些道理了
This is all beginning to make a creepy kind of sense.
上尉  你认为呢?
What do you think about all this, captain?
我想这就是为什么我们没有机会
I think that explains why we never had a chance.
我们所有的策略只是根据一个假定
All our strategies are based on one assumption.
我们是在和外星侵略者作战
That me are fighting alien invaders.
想想那个梦  格雷  他们如何死的
Think of the dream, Gray. How they die?
从那以后  他们只知道受苦
Since then, all they know is suffering.
他们不是侵略的军队
They are not an invading army.
他们是鬼魂
They are ghosts.
有多少幽灵?
How many phantoms?
足够能说服委员会
More than enough to convince the Council, sir.
很好  发一个警报  派一个班去消灭他们
Excellent. Send the squad out to eliminate them.
是  长官
Yes, sir.
警报状态：全面部署
长官  我有许多的幽灵接触
Sir, I have numerous phantoms contacts.
当然
Well, of course you do.
在第31号外面  并迅速的移动
Outside sector 31, sir. And moving in incredible speed.
到底发生什么事?
Major, what the hell is going on here?
他们在导管里
They are in the pipes.
他们在利用生化能量来移动
不可能  没有生物能在这些导管里生存
That's impossible. No living thing could survive in those pipes.
有个大的朝这边过来  巨型的  长官
Well, we got a big one heading this way.
哦  天啊
Oh my god...
别开火！
Hold your fire!
我做了什么?
What have I done?
快点  尼尔  我们需要办法  你是我们可靠的人  快想办法
Come on, Neil. We need to find a way out. Now think.
上尉  这些墙是钛合金做的  这屏障是脉冲激光
Captain, these wall titanium alloy. And the bars are all pole sonic lasers.
我不能晃一下魔棒…
I mean is not like I can just wave a magic wont and...
-尼尔  我很感动 -我也是
-Neil, I'm impressed. -That makes two of us.
前往最近的撤离地点
Proceed to the nearest evacuation facility.
我想我们应该前往最近的撤离地点
I think we should proceed to the nearest evacuation facility.
-他们来了 -还有其他的！希德博士！
-Here they come. -But the others... Dr. Sid!
深遂眼睛队员会保护他的  我们走吧
Deep Eyes will take care of him. Come on!
出了什么事?我们为什么现在能看到他们?
What's happening? Why can we see them now?
他们一定是带着屏障上的残留电荷
It must be carry resistible charge passing through the barrier.
注意你后面！
Behind you!
全部到齐  上尉
On the board, captain.
我们需要去找我的船
We must find my ship.
如果它被拖回来  它应该搁在飞机棚里
If it was towed inside the city, it could be in the military hangar.
注意这是很重要的如果
That's a big 'If'.
注意
Look out!
-把我们带到平台上去 -明白
- Get us out of the platform. - You got it.
好了  现在怎么办?
Okay, now what?
我们要穿过车站
We're going through the station.
-什么? -上尉  和所有有关系的
- What? -Captain, with all respect...
对不起  长官
- Excuse me, captain...
我们要去的
We're going through it.
这是唯一的路
It's the only way.
我看这是个困难的行程
Should I gather all this will be somehow a rough ride.
你很会低估啊
Doc, you got a talent for understatement.
坚持住  各位
Hang on, everybody.
博士?
Doc?
很有意思
Interesting.
-有没有人受伤? -上尉
-Anybody hurt? -Captain!
哦  天  和我说话 中士
Oh God! Talk to me, sergeant.
噢！
-帮我一下  简 -好
- Give me a hand, Jane. - No, wait!
别动  这太危险了  可能伤得更重要找一些适当的工县  把他弄出来
We're risking for the injury. We need the proper tools to cut him out.
在我的船上有
They are in my ship.
-不  不  博士  别用药 -上尉?
-No! No, Doc.No drugs. - Captain...
你听到了
You heard the man.
我们会找到船的  我们会回来找你
We'll find the ship and we'll be back for you.
-我和他留下 -我也是
- I'll stay with him. - Me too.
谁也别留下
Nobody's staying.
给我一支枪
Just give me a gun.
给他一个武器  去！
You got it. Give him a weapon.Do it!
我们会为你回来
We'll be back for you, sergeant.
你听到没?
You hear me?
我听到了  上尉  现在  离开这里
I hear you, captain. Now get out of here.
我们快走吧
Let's move out.
四轮的ATV  这个很棒
Aqua isolated T.V. This is good.
它可用来接莱恩  并将他安全带回来
It can be used to retrieve Ryan and transport him safely here.
但是我们需要换掉这些燃料罐
However we need to replace this plane's fuel
在飞机棚里可能些“卵包”
There could be some lives overpack in the hangar.
简  去检查飞机棚  尼尔  准备起飞
Alright, Jane. Check the hangar. Neil, get us ready for take off.
阿琪和希德博士  准备好着陆车
Aki and Dr. Sid prep the quad troll.
我去指挥塔  转航道
I'll go to the tower and rotate the air track.
这城市或许完了  但不是我们  让我们快一点离开
The city maybe lose. But we are not. Let's do this thing and get the hell out of here.
格雷  小心
Gray...Be careful.
你也是
You too.
哦  是的
Oh yeah.
尼尔  能听到我吗?
Neil, do you read me?
大而清楚  长官
Loud and clear, captain.
这宝贝能自己起飞
This baby would fly itself.
飞行路线安置好了
Flight plane is set.
开始旋转
Beginning rotation.
停止航道碟  我们有个问题
This is not the air track. We have a problem.
一个扣押的拖拉机连接在船上
I'm reading an impound tracks detach to the ship.
你能否将它分离?
Can you disengage it from the cockpit?
批准离开到外面去分离连接
No, sir. Permission to go outside and detach the cockpit.
去吧
Do it!
问题就在这里
There is the problem.
控制器自己锁住了
The controls are locked naturally.
简  我想问问你  我们可以活着离开这里吗?
Jane, let me ask you something.You think we're going to get out here alive?
我不知道有没有人离开过这里
I mean I'm wondering if anybody is getting out
你认为有人能做到吗?
You think anyone had made it this far?
这个第八个灵魂真的能对付幽灵?
You think this 8th spirit stuff is going to work and chase out all the phantoms?
如果它们只是一派胡言怎么办?
I mean what if it is all a bunch of mambo jumbo?
简  我们能不能停止说话  我需要专心
Jane, do you mind if we stop talking? I gotta concentrate here.
下面发生什么事?
What's happening down there.
没有不能处理的
Nothing we can't handle.
-尼尔  怎么样了? -快好了
- What's your status? - Almost there.
你们俩快回里面来
我们很好  长官  简正在带着偏见谈判
We're fine, sir. Jane is negotiating with the extreme residents.
和我说话  简
Talk to me, Jane.
这里没有问题  上尉
No problem here, Captain.
好了！上尉  我们可以出发了
Yes! Captain, we are good to go.
不！
No!
简  离开那里
Jane, get out of there.
现在就离开那里！快走  简！
Get out now! Go!
快离开那里！简！
Get the hell out of there! Jane!
防卫屏已经准备好
Unseal the power and ready.
你去哪里?
Where are you going?
去驾驶室  船现在是自动驾驶的。
To the cockpit. The ship is set on autopilot
起飞已经倒数时了
We are in countdown to leave off.
等一下  这太危险  阿琪！
Wait. It's too dangerous. Aki!
这边  畜牲！
Over here. You son of the bitch.
格雷  你听得见我吗?怎么回事?
Ryan! Gray, do you read me? What's happening?
你和希德要离开这里
You and Sid are getting out of here now.
-不行！我们不能留下大家 -大家都死了
-No! We can't just leave everyone. -Everyone's dead.
-我不要离开你 -对不起  你没有选择余地
I'm sorry. But you don't have a choice.
再见  阿琪
Goodbye, Aki.
格雷  快点！
我只是
I just...
我希望他们能在更好的地方
I wish I could believe they are in a better place.
宙斯
目标确认
我放大了扫描范围
I enlarge the scanning parameter to include an area.
包括了以前我们忽略的地点
冲击坑
The impact crater.
寻找第八灵魂的奇怪地方
That's the strange place to find the ex-spirit.
是很惊人
Yes, really.
除了幽灵  没有东西能在那里生存
But nothing can survive there except phantoms.
准确
Precisely.
这说明第八灵魂就是个幽灵
We suggest that the 8th spirit is a phantom spirit.
现在我不能做解释  不过当我们下去后…
I can't explain it until that moment. But once we get down there...
-你就会明白 -等等  博士  那是有去无回
-You'll understand... - Wait. That's the one way trip.
这就是你对我们机会的评估
Yes. Yes, I expected that's how you'll valuate our chance.
我错了吗?
What am I wrong?
不  我同意  我们可能…
No, I agree. We'll probably
不能活到把第八灵魂取出来
won't live long enough To extract the 8th spirit from the crater...
那为什么要做?
Then why should we try it?
因为我们不需要提取第八灵魂
Because we don't need to extract the 8th spirit.
如果我们不能把这最后的灵魂取到这
We can bring the final spirit here.
我们可以进去和陨石坑里完成波型
We can go there and complete the wave inside the crater.
完全正确
Yes. Exactly.
那么我们究竟从何做起?
And how do we do that... exactly?
我可以建造一个装置
I can construct the device.
能够连接到阿琪的胸板并提取第八幽灵  然后…
That would attach to Aki's chest plate together the eight spirits and then...
然后呢?
And then what?
然后我们就等一会  看看会发生什么
And then we wait. And see what happens.
就这样?
That's it?
这就是你的计划?等待一会?
That's your plan? We wait and see what happens?
很好  我也有我的计划
Yes. Oh good. But I got my own plan.
我们从轨道继续扫描它表面
We keep scanning the surface of orbit.
或许我们能在其它地方找到匹配的灵魂
Maybe we'll find the compatible spirit somewhere else.
阿琪
Aki?
我说我们进去吧
I say we go in.
海因将军  您可以进入阿尔法01
General Hein, you're clear to go in to the zero one alpha.
是什么使屏障失效  海因将军?
What caused the battle failed, General Hein?
我想幽灵能产生出对我们屏障的抗体  只是时间的问题
I'm afraid it's only the matter of time before the phantoms develop into immunity to our barriers.
很高兴看到你和委员会
But I'm ready to see you and the rest of the Council
能平安撤退到休士顿
to evacuate to Houston without incident.
今晚我们损失惨重
It was a terrible suffer this evening.
委员会重新考虑你的建议去发射宙斯炮
The Council had reconsidered your proposal fire the Zeus cannon.
我知道了
I see.
我们现在传送密码给你
We are transmitting the access code to you now.
将军  愿我们都好运
And General, best of luck to us all.
准备发射大炮
Prepare to fire the cannon.
目标  长官?
Target, sir?
幽灵陨石坑
The phantom crater.
里海山脉：幽灵陨石坑
准备投放  三  二  一
Prepare to drop in three, two, one.
启动防护屏障
Powering the shield.
我们已经过了陨星
Okay, we are over the mini one.
你能看见它吗  博士?
Do you have it inside, Doctor.
他们有很多
There are so many of them?
等一下
Wait.
是的  我在弹坑的表面搜寻第八灵魂
Yes. I'm tracking the 8th spirit moving along the crater surface.
好的  让我们靠近点去看看
Alright. Now let's take a closer look.
三分钟后发射准备就绪
Ready to fire in 3 minutes.
卵包能量最大  自动传送等离子体流
Overpack set maximum. Transferring class to other.
反推进器启动
Counter thrusters are engaged.
流通离散  绿色状况
Locks flow the couple. Status is green.
雷达显示陨石冲击处有东西  长官
We have something in the radar over the impact side, sir.
是她
It's her.
长官?
Sir.
是个受敌人控制的背叛者
Just a traitor on the influence of the enemy.
继续倒计时
Continue the countdown.
我们把他们全部同时全消灭
We'll take them all out at the same time.
我们接近幽灵了  30秒后接触
We're closing on the phantom. Contact in 30 seconds.
目标锁定
Target locked.
等候你的命令即可发射
Ready to fire on your command.
是匹配的！  完美的匹配！
It's a match. It's a perfect match.
-扫描器就绪 -发射
-Target's cannon is ready, sir. -Fire!
那是什么?
What was that?
是宙斯炮  他们在炸陨石坑
It's the Zeus. They're firing on the crater.
-阿琪  上尉  你们还好吗? -有一点摇晃  等一下…
Aki, Gray, are you alright? -A little shaking. Stand by.
希德  第八灵魂不在我们的扫描器上  你有没有?
Sid, the 8th spirit is not on our scanner. Do you have it?
第八灵魂…已经被消灭了
The 8th has been destroyed.
-我们现在怎么办? -任务已经结束了
-What are we going to do now? -Nothing. This mission is over.
-我们离开这里吧 -有情况
-We have to get out of here. -Incoming!
那是什么?
What is that?
你如果要让我们出去  最好就是现在
If you gonna get us out of here, you better do it now.
等一下
Hold on!
我不能抓住你
I can't hold on to you.
不能保持高度
I'm not able to maintain.
紧急降落程序
Emergency landing procedures.
进来  请进来
Come in, come in, please
阿琪  格雷  你们能听见我吗?
Aki, Gray, can you hear me?
希德  我需要和空间站谈话  你能不能帮我们接过去?
Sid, I need to talk to the station. Can you pass us through?
那个是什么东西?我不知道  长官
What is that thing? I don't know, sir.
消息传入  长官
Incoming message, sir.
海因将军  你必须马上停止发射
General Hein, you must cease fire immediately.
你看到的是外星人世界的幽灵
What are you looking at, in the crater is the living spirit of an alien's home world.
他们的星球被毁灭了  星球的部分降落在这里
The planet was destroyed and part of the it landed here.
这不是入侵  从来就不是
This is not an invasion. It never was.
我知道了  我们一直与之战斗是什么  博士?幽灵吗?
Oh, I see. And what we have been fighting all this time, Doctor? Ghosts?
是的  迷失  混乱  和生气的灵魂
Yes, spirits that are confused, lost and angry.
是的  这些幽灵是从盖亚神而来的
Oh right? And these spirits are coming out of the Gaya,
海因将军  你必须听
外星的盖亚  地球的盖亚  博士  即使我相信这些
Earth Gaya. Doctor, even if I believe in such nonsense.
事实仍然是地球被一个侵略者袭击
The fact remains the Earth is under attack
我们必须不惜一切代价消灭它
from aggressor who must be destroyed at all cost.
而这代价可能是整个星球的  长官
The cost maybe the entire planet, sir.
袭击外星的盖亚只会让它更加强大
Fire on the alien Gaya would only make it stronger.
既然你受外星人的影响  博士
Since that you under the alien influence, Doctor.
我想你的抗议只能说明我们正在采取正确的行动
I will take your protest to mean, we are in fact persuading the correct course of action.
预备好你们最后的时刻准备去见盖亚
I suggest you take your last few months and prepare to meet your Gaya.
继续射击直到侵略者被毁灭
Continue to fire until the invaders have been destroyed.
将军  系统过热
General, this is the mis-over-hitting.
我们继续袭击直到它完全灭亡
We are going to hit again and again. And keep on hitting it, until it's dead.
可是我们不确定这是不是有用
But sir, we not even sure if it has any affect on the other creature.
没有用? 我们令他们逃跑  军人
No affect. We got them in the run, soldier.
这是我们胜利的时刻  我命令你发射
This is the moment of our victory. order you to fire.
-系统不允许我们再发射 -让我们看一看吧
-This won't allow us to fire again. We'll see about that.
我们的防护屏没了  我们在这是坐以待毙  快点
Now shield is out, we're seeking Doc in here. Come on.
这不是个好地方
This is not a good place to be.
那是什么?它是我想的东西吗?
What the hell is that? That's something I'm thinking, is it?
是的  是盖亚
Yes! It's Gaya.
这决不是个好地方
Definitely not a good place to be.
你没事吧?
Are you alright?
我没事  我必须和希德博士说话
I'm fine. I have to talk to Dr. Sid.
希德  你听得到我吗?
Sid, do you read me?
可以  我还在这里
Go ahead. I'm still here.
我们看见了盖亚  你听到了吗  希德?盖亚
We are looking at Gaya. You hear me, sir? Gaya!
这就是为什么第八灵魂出现在这里
I think this explains why the ex-spirits appeared here.
是的  这就对了！
Yes. Yes, that's it.
一个幽灵变成了第八灵魂
A phantom must have changed into the 8th spirit
从我们的盖亚里出生
when it starts a new life born on our own Gaya.
如果是这样  它可以得到一个不同的能源记号
If so, it would have been given a different energy signature
把它和其他幽灵区分开来
that set apart from the other phantoms.
这里是找一个新的匹配灵魂最好的地方了
You two could not have hope for better location to find a new compatible spirit.
不管你做什么  别动  停留在那里
Whatever you do, don't move. Stay right where you are.
留在这里不是你想的那样容易
Staying right where we are may not be as easy as it sound.
不要射击他们！
Don't shoot any of them.
你很可能毁掉我们最后的希望
You could destroy our last hope.
你有什么提议?请他们态度好一点吗?
And what do you suggest I do, Doctor? Ask them to play nice?
战斗策略是你的专长  上尉  不是我的
Combat strategy is your area of expertise, not mine.
我看到在裂缝里有指示  你看到没有?
I have a reading here in official. Do you see it?
有的！是一个匹配的幽灵  它一定很靠近你
Yes, a compatible spirit. It must be very near you.
哪一个是它呢?
Where? Which one is it?
哪一个?
Which one?
很难看清  请等一下
I'm having difficulty now. Just a moment.
这里很拥挤  阿琪  我们没有时间
Doctor, it's getting crowded in here. We don't have much time.
阿琪！阿琪！！
Aki...Aki!
为了新生命的希望
With the hope of new life,
盖亚有没有改变里面的幽灵?
has Gaya changed the phantom within?
我找到它了
I have it.
格雷  进里面来  我需要你
Gray, get in here. I need you.
听见没有  希德?波型图完成了
Do you hear me, Sid?The wave pattern is completed.
是的  我听到了  这太棒了
Yes, I read you. This is wonderful.
我不知道你怎么找到最后的灵魂
I don't see how you could have found the final spirit.
是它找到我  博士
It found me, Doctor.
哦  天
我现在知道了  懂了
I see now. I understand.
我不明白！怎么回事?
I don't understand. What the hell is going on?
给我你的卵包  我需要它来发射完整的波
Give me your overpack. I need to project it in the complete way.
-但是我们就会失去防卫 -你就给我吧！
We'll be defenseless.
-我希望你知道你在做什么  阿琪 -我们可以用它来发射波
-I hope you know what you are doing, Aki. -We can use the shield to project the wave.
-什么? -希德博士的理论是对的  我找到了  第八幽灵
Dr Sid's theory was right. I have it, the 8th spirit.
我已经复原了  格雷
I'm cured, Gray.
-你确定你有最后的灵魂吗 -是的  我确定
-Are you sure you have the final spirit? -Yes, yes. I'm sure.
-你如何知道? -别担心  一个幽灵告诉我的
-But how? How can you know that? -Don't worry, the phantom told me.
哦  很棒
Oh, great.
好了  防护屏启动
That's it. Shield on.
它不行了  我们得在太迟之前想点办法
It's not working. We have to do something before it's too late.
如果这个不行  那么就真是太晚了
If this doesn't work, then it's already too late.
格雷  相信我
Gray... trust me.
我要把你们炸到地狱去
哦  不  不！
No! No!
下来！
Get down!
-警告  系统超载 -我知道
-Warning system overload. -I know.
-Warning system overload. -I know!
可是必须完成
But it must be done.
发射
Fire!
发射  王八蛋！
Fire! Damn it!
发射！
Fire!
格雷  格雷
Gray? Gray!
不要离开我  格雷
Don't leave me, Gray.
早就告诉希德这是有去无回
I told you this was an one-way trip.
看来我说对了
Looks like I was right.
不  格雷  坚持一下
No, Gray. Hang on, please.
我仍然有波
I still have the wave.
我们可以解决的
We can get through this.
我们做不到  我们做得到
We are going to make it. We are going to make it.
我们都知道那不是真的
We both know that isn't time.
格雷
Gray...
帮助我
Help me.
听我说
Listen to me.
你救过我  现在我要你救你自己
You saved my life once. Now I want you to save yourself.
格雷  不要  拜托！
Gray, no. Please.
让我来吧  阿琪  相信我
Let me do this, Aki. Trust me.
不要离开我  格雷
Don't leave me, Gray.
你一直在努力告诉我死亡不是结束
You have been trying to tell me death isn't the end.
不要骗我  现在我终于相信
Don't back out on me. Now I finally believe.
我爱你
I love you.
哦  好温暖
Oh, it's warm.
释放内心的梦想
群星落泪
天堂叹息
世界终了
释放内心的梦想
神秘莫测
我们摇摆旋转
心灵飞升
用心守望远方
梦想和平
互信互爱
我们摇摆旋转
心灵飞升
释放内心的梦想
歌声在召唤
你内心的祈祷
将指引你
实现内心的梦想
阳光照耀
风中火光闪亮
拯救从此开始
用心守望远方
梦想和平
互信互爱
我们摇摆旋转
心灵飞升
啊…